what's up everyone 10805 here with a
very special video today now you're not
gonna believe this [__] like I've got
like I've got a crazy story to tell you
that's something why I have today
something so wild at the moment I got
home I put my [__] pants like you're
not gonna believe this [__] anyways like
this has to do with like Julia why and
Phil Hayes like for those who don't know
like Julia why is the voice actor of
Sonic the Hedgehog from Sonic
Underground and like Phil Hayes is the
voice actor of Soccer Boy socks
boyfriend Bobby and [__] you know how it
is anyways like I met them like I you
can make this [__] up I went I went down
to like Quick Trip like early this
morning because I was like I was I'm a
soccer fan like you hear me like I'm
like some days I'm in the mood for
chilly dog some days I'm in the mood to
take a [__] and that today I was just in
the mood to like you know how [__]
Julia so I wanna have the cricket for
those who don't know quick trip it's
like a it's like a shitty night I was
damn I was about to say 9 11. like a
Christian is like a shitty 7-Eleven a
shitty seven eleven you know what that
is anyways like I go down there for like
uh for Zone like
and they are I'll show you that because
you know that's like the official meal
for psycho apprenticeship and anyways
when I went inside like I I ran into
them Julia why and Phil Hayes now I
don't know what the [__] they were doing
there I saw them coming in and here's
the crazy part I'm like
but Phil Hayes was speaking of Bobby's
like voice from the TV show Angela was
like speaking in his Sonic voice
because you know like they're the voice
actors like I thought what the [__] is
going on like is it some kind of erotic
role play or some [__] and he was like
uh you're not gonna believe this like I
saw them going to get like a slushie
well I was getting chilly and then they
approached me [__] like I didn't
approach them like Jalil why and
the Phil Hayes like approached me and
we're like yo tamas one two three four
five from YouTube is is that you and
they recognized it because I was like
one like my Barbie costume and [__] like
I I always well whenever I go down to
Quick Trip and I get my chili dogs
they're like my frozen yeah because
because that's what we said that's what
we do that's what we do at soccer on
fans anyways like they they're like I
was like hell yeah it is but here's the
crazy thing they never stopped acting
like sock and bottle B like for like
five minutes they were like
they were just talking to us talk about
me I was like this is getting weighted
this is getting weird
anyways like Bobby
Phil Hayes that Phil Hayes he eventually
stopped like he asked me about for my
autographs I asked for his his were cool
like that like although like Julie why
he kept doing it he kept talking at
Sonic and like I think I even whispered
to all that I mean I think I think I
heard Julia I wish with you feeling Haze
it was like can you spank my ass daddy
like Bobby can you spank my ass and Phil
Hayes like I think I saw him pushing him
off like it was weird like I don't know
I don't know what that was about but
anyways like
me and Phil Hayes we were chatting up a
storm talking about my videos and how
much he loves my [__] and Julia wouldn't
stop like he went over and got like like
got like a frizoni he came back well he
went over to the bathroom and he like
told Phil Hayes is like like hey Bobby
I'm gonna go go take a [__] like can you
come like I'll I don't know like heal me
like stand there while I wash my hands
or some [__] and Phil Hayes he was like
yeah yeah well one second Julia like I'm
talking to us and Julia were like I'm
waiting like Chuck just like Sonic like
just like [__] on the ground I can't
deny like I thought that was kind of
cool like
me and Phil we just had to walk up to
jail and we had to say that like Julia
you gotta stop there was one pound where
like I put my hand on like on like like
Julia I was like at least listen like
Julia you gotta stop and then he like
pushed my hand away and also he stopped
the role playing in Sonic and he saw
role playing his Mac and I was like get
your get your ass off me and he like he
almost I think he started stealing [__]
like I don't remember like I think I saw
him grab a couple things he thought but
he was actually manic like I mean I feel
like what the [__] is he doing like why
is he doing this he's embarrassing us he
is embarrassing sock I'm gonna go fast
like what the [__] what the [__] like me
and Phil what do we do in this situation
like Jaleel if you're watching this
video you need to stop I forgot to tell
you how long you were talking Sonic like
let me let me put it this way me and
Phil like when Phil and Joey came in
they were doing the erotic role play
maybe three minutes after I I approached
them but Julia like he kept it going
[__] for 45 minutes so Julia you don't
you don't do that in quick trip